It truly is a beautiful planet.
本当に美しい星
I could gaze upon it forever.
何度見ても心を奪われます
Does seeing the planet of your birth
make you homesick?
あなたも懐かしいですか　生まれ故郷が
Slaine?
スレイン
Um... Yeah, it does.
えっと　それは　まぁ…
Don't be shy.
照れる事はありません
I've only been away for two months,
but I already miss Vers.
私だって　たった二ヶ月留守にしただけで
もうヴァースが恋しいですもの
Earth...
地球…
The birthplace of us all. Of mankind.
私達人類の発祥の地
I've always dreamed of
seeing it with my own eyes.
昔から　この目で見るのが夢だったのです
R-Right.
は　はぁ…
Hey, Slaine.
ねぇ　スレイン　空も青くて海も青いというけれど
They say your skies and seas are blue,
and I've always thought that was a little strange.
前から不思議だったんです
Is there blue coloring in your air and water?
地球では　水や空気に青い色が付いているんでしょうか
No.
いえ　水や空気は透明です
Water and air are transparent.
But when the sun's light passes through a lot at once, it gets scattered, and...
ただそれが大量に積み重なると　光の屈折とか　ありまして
i-it looks blue... to us.
あ　青い色に　見える
I think that's the explanation.
って事だと思うんです
To think there is so much air and water that it bends light!
光を歪めるほどたくさんの　水と空気
That's astounding!
凄いですね　想像も付きません
I can't even imagine it!
So this is where you are.
こちらにおいででしたか
Count Cruhteo.
クルーテオ伯爵
The hour is quite late.
夜もだいぶ更けて参りました
どうか御寝所へ　お戻りになられますよう
Please return to your chambers,
Princess Asseylum.
アセイラム姫
Oh my, is it really that late already?
あら　もうそんな時間
When I gaze out from this terrace, time passes in the blink of an eye.
このテラスからの眺めは　つい時を忘れてしまいますね
Then I shall retire, Slaine.
それではスレイン
I look forward to learning more from you tomorrow.
また明日の授業も　よろしくお願いしますね
Y-You honor me, my lady.
は…はい　恐縮です
With just three days left until the
goodwill visit by Asseylum Vers Allusia,
「火星　ヴァース帝国の第一皇女
アセイラム・ヴァース・アリューシア姫の親善訪問を三日後に控え」
first princess of the Martian Vers Empire,
tension is rising across an otherwise welcoming Earth.
「各地では歓迎の気運と同時に　緊張も高まっています」
Though the visit is aimed at easing the relationship between the two planets, opinions are divided.
「火星と地球　惑星間の緊張緩和に向けた今回の皇女外遊…」
Morning, Inaho.
なお君　おはよ…
Morning, Yuki.
おはよ　ユキ姉
Which would you have preferred, an omelet or scrambled eggs?
だし巻き卵とスクランブルエッグは　どっちが良かったかな
I feel like an omelet today.
だし巻き卵かなぁ
My condolences. I made scrambled eggs.
残念　今日はスクランブルエッグ
Aren't you having any?
なお君　朝ごはんは
I already ate.
もう食べたよ
Aren't you cutting it a bit close, though?
ユキ姉こそいいの　今日は訓練教官シフトだろ
I thought you were on instructor duty today.
Why didn't you wake me?!
何で起こしてくれなかったのよ
Believe me, I tried,
何度も起こしたよ　界塚准尉
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
Wait!
ちょっと待ってよ
Don't worry.
大丈夫　次のバスでも　走ればぎりぎり間に合うよ
Even if you catch the next bus,
you should make it in time if you run.
Just speaking from experience here.
経験則として参考までに
Oh, and could you leave the dishes in the sink? Thanks.
洗い物は流しによろしくね
Damn, he's ice-cold.
薄情者…
And so, Apollo 17 discovered the remnants
of an ancient civilization on the Moon's surface.
こうして　アポロ17号により月面で発見された
Astronaut Eugene Cernan standing on the Moon
古代火星文明の遺産　ハイパーゲートは
Excavated Hypergate
The Hypergate they found opened the door for mankind to settle and terraform Mars.
人類に火星への移住と　開拓の道を開きました
Mars, pre-settlement
Excavated Hypergate
However, the Vers Empire then emerged,
Ancient ruins discovered on Mars
しかしその結果　火星の遺跡とその古代テクノロジー
Martian Ancient Technology, "Aldnoah"
laying sole claim to the ruins on Mars and
Aldnoah, the ancient technology found there.
「アルドノア」の占有を主張するヴァース帝国の出現と
Martian Ancient Technology, "Aldnoah"
Count Rayregalia (later first Emperor of the Vers Empire) speaks to the settlers
This would be the source of conflicts for many years to come.
長きに渡る戦乱の原因にもなったのです
Count Rayregalia (later first Emperor of the Vers Empire) speaks to the settlers
Hey there, Inaho!
よう伊奈帆
Morning.
おはよ
Hey, where's Yuki?
あれっ　ユキさんと一緒じゃないの
She overslept.
姉貴は寝坊
If she works up some determination,
she can still make it to the drill in time.
まあ根性を見せたら　兵科教練には間に合うんじゃないかな
Hey, we're heartbroken here.
何だよ　我らが火曜日の女神のエスコートをすっぽかすなんて
How could you show up
without our Tuesday Goddess?
Who is she, Penivia?
ペニビアかな
What?
何?
The goddess of sloth.
怠惰の女神
She's got the right idea.
怠惰賛成
進学希望にとっちゃ　兵科教練なんて関係無えんだしっ…
What use do college aspirants have for drills?
You've got lofty goals for someone who failed his midterms, Okojo.
進学希望も何も　オコジョは中間考査で赤点　食らってたろ
カームだって　この前の行動演習　C-だろうがよ
Didn't you get a C- during the
last maneuver yourself, Calm?
I've covered the material
backwards and inside out!
私は筆記対策ばっちしだからね
Time to snatch back that top rank!
今度こそ　学年首席の座を取り戻すんだから
You seem really fired up to beat Inaho, Inko.
打倒伊奈帆君に燃えてるんだよねぇ　韻子は
Still recovering, huh?
災害復興かぁ
I guess even here in Shin-awara
the areas outside town still need time.
新芦原も市街を離れれば　まだまだだなぁ
It's been fifteen years since Heaven's Fall.
「ヘブンズ・フォール」から15年
The Martians sure went to town on the place, huh?
やりたい放題だよな　火星の野郎共がよ
Japan's doing pretty well, relatively speaking.
日本はまだマシな方だよ　俺やニーナの所に比べりゃ
Nina and I have seen much worse.
But the Martians have been
extending the olive branch, right?
でも今は　火星も協調路線なんでしょう
ほら　今度親善大使が来るって
I mean, they're sending a goodwill ambassador and everything!
Yeah, the Vers princess.
あぁ　ヴァースの姫様ね
What was her name again?
何てったっけ　アセ…アセ…
Ass—
Uh...
さっすが赤点
No wonder you failed.
Shut up.
うっせーよ
In 1999, the Vers Empire finally
declared war on the Terran Federation.
「1999年　ヴァース帝国はついに地球連合へ宣戦を布告」
After a long and fierce battle
on the Moon's surface,
「月面での激しい攻防戦の結果」
the Hypergate went out of control, destroying the Moon,
「暴走したハイパーゲートは　月そのものを破壊」
thus ending its 4.5-billion-year
lifespan as our satellite.
「およそ45億年に渡って　地球の衛星であり続けた…」
I'm sorry I'm late!
遅れて申し訳ありません
What remains of the Moon now orbits Earth as the Satellite Belt.
Hey there, Warrant Officer Sleepyhead.
よう　寝坊助准尉
Lieutenant Marito...
鞠戸大尉
That reeks!
臭っ
Didn't I ask you to lay off the booze on drill days?
兵科教練の日は　お酒を抜いてくださいとお願いしましたよね　大尉
They're just playing with toys.
どうせお遊戯だ　そう気負うな
Don't get so worked up.
We're doing live-fire exercises today.
今日は実弾演習ですよ
Activate master arm switch...
マ…マスターアームスイッチ…
Locate fire control...
ファイヤーコントロール…
Lower the dampers and lock on...
ダンパー下ろしてロックオン…
Adjust the sights, and...
照準補正…
F—
ファ…ファイヤー!
Fire!
Okay, switch pilots.
おーし　パイロット交代
B班はスタンドに退避
Team B, go to the stands.
They're in your hands,
Warrant Officer Kaizuka.
誘導を頼む　界塚准尉
Go easy on the booze, okay?
ほどほどにお願いしますね
A drunk drill instructor
would set a terrible example.
お酒臭い先生なんて　生徒に示しがつきませんよ
心配するな　軽蔑されるのは慣れてる
Don't worry about me.
I'm used to being looked down on.
I disagree.
いいえ
Deep down, you're a fine soldier, Lieutenant Marito.
あなたは本当は立派な軍人です　鞠戸大尉
I thought I warned you to cut down on the alcohol, Lieutenant.
酒量は減らすように注意しましたよね　大尉
Well hello, Doctor Yagarai.
おや　耶賀頼先生
Rare to see you here.
珍しい
Long way to come on a house call.
こんな所にまで訪問診察とは…
My patient likes to test my patience.
厄介な担当患者のおかげでね
飲まなきゃやってられんさ
This is what keeps me going.
I had to run more of their drills today.
今日もあいつらの共同演習だった
The work you do is indispensable, you know.
それも立派なお仕事ですよ
The KG-6 Sleipnir...
KG-6スレイプニール
Developed by the United Forces of Earth to meet
the imminent Martian threat, it is a Cataphract—
来たるべき火星の脅威に備えて開発された連合軍のカタフラクト
a manned, humanoid weapon.
有人人型兵器
今やこいつの軍事教練は全ての高校の必修科目だ
Training in its use is now a required subject at all high schools.
75ミリ砲をお遊戯みたいにぶっ放し
They fire 75mm cannons like toy guns,
believing they'll save their country one day.
お前らはこれで立派に故郷を守れると
And it's my job to indoctrinate them with that nonsense?
こんな馬鹿げた戯れ言を子供に吹き込むのが仕事だと?
What a joke.
冗談じゃねぇ
大尉
Lieutenant...
15年前　種子島の出来事を　上層部は握りつぶした
The brass already covered up the
Tanegashima affair fifteen years ago.
Nobody believes the truth anymore.
今じゃもう誰も信じていない
だが俺だけは覚えてる
But I remember, even if nobody else does.
アルドノア
Aldnoah...
They found the power of God on Mars.
火星でやつらは神の力を手に入れた
The ruins of a civilization
that died out 30,000 years ago.
3万年前の古代文明の遺産を
An absurd power strong enough to reduce the moon to rubble.
月そのものを粉々に砕いちまった途方も無い力を
そんな物に立ち向かうってのがどういう事か　誰もまじめに考えようとしない
How's anyone supposed to
stand up to something like that?
Nobody's taking this seriously.
They think this fleeting peace will last forever.
今の様な仮初めの平和がずっと続くと信じてる
Hey, Doctor.
なあ先生
When the shit hits the fan out there, what's gonna happen to those kids?
俺達大人からデタラメを吹き込まれたあのガキ共は一体どうなっちまうんだ
How will they face the lions who've been
sharpening their claws on the remnants of the moon?
いつかあいつらが　月の残骸の中で牙を研いでいる連中と向き合った時
How will we atone for the lies we fed them?
俺達はどうやって　この嘘の落とし前をつければいい
スレイン
Slaine.
Princess Asseylum.
アセイラム姫
面を上げてください　スレイン
You may rise, Slaine.
Thank you.
はっ
I must bid you farewell.
お別れの日が来てしまいました
I will go to Earth now to fulfill
my duty as goodwill ambassador.
私はこれより地球に降りて　親善の務めを果たします
I'm sure all the knowledge you imparted will prove useful.
あなたに教わった様々な知識が　きっと役に立つ事でしょう
Won't you be in danger?
その…危険ではないのですか
恐れては立ち行きません
Fear solves nothing.
If Mars and Earth are to one day walk together,
someone must take the first step.
今は火星と地球が歩み寄るための第一歩を
誰かが踏み出さねばならないのです
姫…
Princess...
This is for you.
これを
On Earth, we say these charms protect from evil spirits.
地球に伝わる　魔除けのお守りだと聞いています
But is this not a memento of your father?
でも　これはお父様の形見だと…
Please take it.
いいんです　父も喜ぶと思います
My father would be happy for you to.
Consider it thanks for saving me and my father five years ago, when we were on the verge of death.
5年前　瀕死の僕と父を救ってくれた
そのお礼です　どうか
Please.
あなたとお父上の平和の祈りを　必ずや青い星に届けて参ります
I will deliver your and your father's prayers of peace to the blue planet.
ありがとう　スレイン
Thank you, Slaine.
Princess Asseylum, your shuttle is ready.
アセイラム　シャトルが到着しております
分かりました　それでは
I understand.
Goodbye.
はい
Know your place, worm.
身の程をわきまえよ　下郎
Trying to dissuade the princess from her folly is beyond even one of my station.
このクルーテオが姫の気まぐれをお諌めするなど恐れ多いが
And when a dog soils the carpet, his master is responsible.
犬の粗相は飼い主が責を負う
次は無いぞ　地球人
I won't be so nice next time, Terran.
Yes, sir.
はい
Do you also consider Slaine
to be beneath you, Eddelrittuo?
あなたもスレインの事を良く思っていないのですか　エデルリッゾ
え…まあ　その…
Huh?
Um, well...
私達とて　遡ればあの青い星から旅立った移民の末裔
We too are descended from those of the blue planet,
however long ago it may seem.
So why is it that we despise them so?
何故そこまで彼らを忌み嫌うのでしょう
If I may, my lady.
恐れながら
When the first emperor of Vers
inherited the authority of Aldnoah,
初代ヴァース皇帝がアルドノアの威光を受け継いでより
his subjects became an entirely different race from those left on Earth.
我ら帝国の臣民は　地球に居残った旧人類とは　一線を画す種族となったのです
As the one who stirs the power of God to life, Princess,
you in particular should be more aware of what you say.
分けても姫様は神の力を呼び覚ます身の上
あまり滅多なことは…
It is my hope that friendly relations can be established with our distant former home.
私は　遠き故郷たるあの星と　友好的な関係を望んでいます
過去の経緯はどうあれ
Regardless of the past, it is to show amity
and goodwill that I make this visit to Earth.
私は友誼と親愛を示す為にこそ　地球を訪問するのです
Princess...
姫様…
Selena, Hohmann transfer orbit completed.
セレーナ号　フォーマン・トランスファー軌道を終了
これより　降下シークエンスを開始します
Initiating descent sequence.
後は無事を祈る事しかできん
Her safety is in God's hands now.
閣下　ザーツバルム城より通信です
Sir, you have a call from Saazbaum Castle.
Should I put it through?
お繋ぎしますか
Please.
After three months of babysitting, you must be itching to spread your wings, Count Cruhteo.
三ヶ月余りの接待役　さぞや肩が凝ったのではないのか　クルーテオ伯
お務めを果たせたとは言い切れぬ
I cannot say I performed my duty as best I could.
It was my last chance to change her mind about this trip, and I failed.
此度の外遊を思いとどまっていただく　最後の瀬戸際であったというのに
You need not worry yourself.
心配には及ぶまい
If anything should happen to the princess,
我らが姫にもしもの事があれば
軌道上に駐屯する37家門が黙ってはおらぬ
the Thirty-Seven Clans in orbit
will react swiftly and decisively.
Surely the Terrans have learned this by now.
地球の連中とて心得ているであろう
I pray that it is so.
だといいが
But if, perchance, their intentions were always to provoke a battle,
あるいは…
元よりやつらが喧嘩を売る気でいるのなら
then that could be beneficial
to us in its own way.
それはそれで我らとしても渡りに船という物だ
Saazbaum, mind your tongue!
ザーツバルム　滅多な事を言うな
Did I say too much?
言葉が過ぎたかな
You must realize that we Orbital Knights
だが我ら機動騎士は15年
父の代よりこの城で時を待ち続けてきたのだ
have waited fifteen years in our castles since the time of our fathers.
Each day dreaming of the moment when that blue brilliance would be within our grasp.
あの青き輝きに手が届く日を夢見て
The day's finally here, huh?
いよいよですね
Yeah. All those years of lying low are about to pay off.
あぁ　長きに渡る雌伏が今　報われるのだ
There it is.
ご覧ください
ただ今　火星の第一皇女
The limousine carrying Asseylum Vers Allusia, First Princess of Mars, has drawn into view.
アセイラム・ヴァース・アリューシア殿下を載せたリムジンが姿を現しました
It is heading this way with its entourage as we speak.
護衛の車を従え…
間に合った間に合った
We made it!
…ゆっくりとこちらへと近づいて参ります
We seriously could've just watched it on TV.
テレビ中継で十分だって
Well, it's a goodwill visit, right? The crowds need all the extra voices they can get.
まっ　一応親善訪問って名目なわけだし
俺達だって賑わせてやんないと
We need to make them feel welcome.
歓迎ムードってやつ
Man, when did your heart start bleeding for the Martians?
お前　いつから火星親派に鞍替えしたんだよ
だって皇女様だよ　プリンセスよ
This is a high-class lady here. A princess!
And everyone online's saying she's totally cute.
結構可愛い顔してるってネットで噂なんだよ
You're kidding, right?
そっちかよ
Oh!
見えん
Can't see her.
Well, duh.
そりゃまぁな
That's 200mm-thick tinted bulletproof glass.
厚さ200ミリの防弾スモークガラス
Standard issue these days
for vehicles that carry VIPs.
今時の要人護送用特殊車両としちゃあ　珍しくない仕様だなぁ
What, so she's not gonna wave? What kind of parade is this?
何　振らないの　手とか
パレードなのに?
知らねぇよ　セキュリティー対策じゃねえの
Don't ask me. Must be a security measure.
Then why'd we bother coming?
じゃあ俺達は何しに来たんだ
You're the one who wanted to come!
お前が来たいって言ったんだ
Eggs are on sale.
Domestic Eggs (Medium)
10 eggs
1 carton
1 per customer
yen
Today only!
たまご特売
そしてお前はマイペースすぎる
And you're always lost in your own little world.
I knew you'd be here!
やっぱり来てた
Oh, Inko. You came to watch, too?
おお　韻子
お前も見物か
I'm here with the student council.
生徒会
The security guys asked us to help direct traffic.
警備隊の要請で　交通整理手伝ってんの
Look at you, working hard.
そりゃまたご苦労なこって
Hey, if you've got time to hang around here, lend us a hand!
ねぇ　三人とも暇してるんなら手伝ってよ
This place is packed!
もうすっごい人で
猫の手だって借りたいくらいなんだから
Seriously, I'll take anyone with functional limbs at this point!
Meh.
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Send
Select
Sub menu
Don't "meh" me!
えーとか言わない
でも俺ら　猫ほど役に立たねぇよ
Limbs or not, I don't think
we'll be of any use to you.
Yeah.
な
腕章付けて　立っててくれるだけでいいからさ
All you have to do is wear the armband and stand around!
What do you think?
どうする
伊奈帆は　手伝ってくれるよね
What about you, Inaho? You'll help, right?
We should get out of here immediately.
今すぐここを離れよう
Huh?
I just saw a missile.
ミサイルが来る
What?!
何だっ
何なのよ
What the hell's going on?
It made it through!
抜けたぞ
リムジンは無事だ
The limousine's okay!
No.
いや…
Huh?
Princess Asseylum wished whole-heartedly for peace,
我らがアセイラム姫の切なる平和への祈りは
only to be viciously struck down by the villainous Terrans!
悪辣なる地球人共の暴虐によって　無残にも踏みにじられた
We of the Vers Empire must answer this atrocity
我らヴァース帝国の臣は　この旧人類の非道に対して
by bringing down the hammer of justice on Old Humanity!
断固正義の鉄槌を下さねばならない
Lend me your ears, proud knights of Mars!
誇り高き火星の騎士達よ　いざ時は来た
The time is at hand!
歴代の悲願たる地球降下の大任
Our magnum opus spanning generations, Operation Earthfall,
will finally come to fruition!
義を以って　今こそ果たすべし
Let justice be done!
クルーテオ様　反応炉　出力97パーセント
Count Cruhteo, reactor output is at 97%. Preparations for launch are complete.
発進準備　完了です
I am the one to blame for not stopping the princess from taking her trip.
姫の地球行きをお諌めしきれなかったのはこのクルーテオの不徳
他の諸公に遅れを取るな
Keep pace with the other lords.
Our only recourse now is to demonstrate our grief through force of arms!
かくなる上は　武を以って弔意を示すのみ
Landing Castles, descend!
揚陸城　降下開始
目標　日本
Your target: Japan!
姫…
Princess.
「衛星軌道上に滞留している　37機の揚陸城の内
We've confirmed that nineteen of the thirty-seven Landing Castles in orbit are on the descent.
19機の降下を確認した
They are predicted to land in New Orleans, as well as Beijing, Mozambique, and Tokyo.
落着予想地点はニューオリンズ
続いて北京　モザンビーク
そして　東京」
One Castle is likely to land within a 20km radius of Ichigaya or Chiyoda,
Haven't these guys ever heard of coordination?
こいつら　連携しようって気がまるで無いんだな
It's just a mad scramble for first landfall. Command's basically non-existent.
我先にと落ちてくるだけで
approximately three hours from now at 0800.
統率も糞も無い
何も分かっちゃいないな
You don't know anything, do you?
While we cannot predict the extent of the damage,
Lieutenant.
大尉…
These guys aren't interested in coordinating anything.
やつらに統率なんて必要無い
we believe the Martians will use this attack to prompt their invasion.
あれは37人の騎士が率いる別個の軍隊だ
There are thirty-seven different knights up there leading thirty-seven self-contained armies.
Therefore, we will deploy approximately fifty kilometers south of the projected impact point,
They're jockeying for first place so they can snap up all the kills.
そいつらが陣取り合戦の為に先を争って降りてくる
and once the shockwave has passed, we will launch a pre-emptive attack.
All they care about is their fellow Mars Knights.
ライバルは同じ火星騎士同士
From our observations, the Castles are
approximately two kilometers in length.
Counterattacks from the surface don't even register as a concern for them.
地上の反撃なんて端から問題にもしちゃいないんだよ
That's sick.
こんなの…
They'd go so far as to unilaterally break the truce?
休戦協定を一方的に破棄してまで
Truce?
休戦?
For fifteen years they've been waging war up where the Moon used to sit.
この十五年間
あいつらは月の残骸の中でずっと戦争を続けて来たんだよ
Fighting to survive until this day.
生き延びて時を待つという　戦いを
Move it, jerk!
早く行けっつうんだよ
How many times do I have to tell you?
だから何度も言ってるだろ
Hey, what's that?
何だあれ
Check out the shooting stars, Sis!
お姉ちゃん見て
流れ星
Wow. Look how many there are!
すごーい　あんなにたくさん
Did you make a wish?
お願い事はした?
You bet!
世界中の人が　仲良く平和に暮らせますようにって
I wished for world peace!
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作，仅供交流学习，禁止用于任何商业用途
日听:つっちー   翻译:mam&低音子   校对:小可&zwx   时间轴:亢奋の蛇   压制:河蟹
君が見る夢は　古いインクで紙に書いた祈りのよう
kimi ga miru yume wa
Your selfless dream
furui inku de kami ni kaita inori no you
is like a prayer written on paper with yellowing ink
chiisana sono te ga sugaru mono mo
Your fragile hands seek support,
小さなその手が　縋るものも　今はまだ何処にも無い
ima wa mada hitori mo nai
and yet have nothing at all to cling to
それでも君の行く道を
sore demo kimi no yuku michi wo
But even so, I want to guard
kirei na mono wa kirei na mama de
the path you walk
奇麗なものは奇麗なままで　守り続けたいと思うよ
mamoritsuzuketai to omou yo
in all my beauty
sora to mizu ga hoshi wo somete
I can see our skies and seas in the stars
空と水が星を染めて
awaku michi wo egaite chitte
before they fall to pave our faint road
淡く虹を描いて散って
眩しい夜　君が歌う
mabushii yoru kimi ga utau
Light tears through the night and you sing
koe wa doko made todoku no darou
How far will your voice travel?
声は何処まで届くのだろう
akogare no sumau aoi hoshi no hikari
This is the light of the blue planet I admire,
憧れの住まう蒼い星のひかり
tada bokura wa koi wo shite
the light that we love helplessly
ただ僕らは恋をして
tatta hitotsu no mirai no tame ni
We sacrifice all we have at our disposal
たったひとつの未来の為に
ima no subete kanadeteiru
for the only future we have left
今の全て奏でてみる
飛び立つよ　まだ暗い空へ
tobitatsu yo
Let us fly
mada kurai sora he
into the blackened sky